{
    "Card 1":{
        "prompt": "2+2",
        "answer": "4",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 2":{
        "prompt": "2x2",
        "answer": "4",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 3":{
        "prompt": "2-2",
        "answer": "0",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 4":{
        "prompt": "12-2",
        "answer": "10",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 5":{
        "prompt": "12x2",
        "answer": "24",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 6":{
        "prompt": "10-2",
        "answer": "8",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 7":{
        "prompt": "10x2",
        "answer": "20",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 8":{
        "prompt": "12-4",
        "answer": "8",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 9":{
        "prompt": "12-6",
        "answer": "6",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    },
    "Card 10":{
        "prompt": "6x2",
        "answer": "12",
        "understood": 10,
        "time":0
    }
}